Recall that each of our PCA components is made up of
我们知道 每个主成分都是
a weighted linear combination of our original features here.
这里的原始特征的加权线性组合
After seeing that the top components account for a large percentage of our data variance,
看到前几个成分可以解释大部分数据方差后
it's interesting to see what exactly the makeup of each component is;
有必要看看每个成分到底是怎么组成的
which features define it.
哪些特征定义了每个成分
So in this next cell, I have
在下个单元格中
a complete function display component that takes in the list of component weights, v,
有一个完整的函数 display_component 它的参数包括成分权重列表 v
our features list which will be the column names from our county's data frame,
特征列表 即 counties dataframe 的列名称
a component number like top one or top two, three, etc.,
成分数量 例如最高成分 前两个 前三个 等等
and a number of top weights to display,
以及要显示的前几个权重的数量
which is any number from 1-34.
它可以是 1-34 之间的任何数字
By default, I'm going to display the top 10 most important feature weights.
默认情况下 我将显示前 10 个最重要的特征权重
Okay. So line-by-line, similar to what we did for the S data frame,
Ok逐行解释下 与 s dataframe 相似
I'm getting the row index of the row that points to our component of interest.
我将获取指向目标成分的行对应的行索引
So just one row that's close to the bottom of our v data frame because the components are
查看靠近 v dataframe 末尾的一行
listed from least to most important in the reverse order that we saw in S as well.
因为成分按照最不重要到最重要排练 与 s 一样
Then I'm getting the list of feature weights for a component,
然后获取成分的特征权重列表
which is that row in our v data frame.
即 v dataframe 中的这行
I'm grabbing the list of weight values.
获取权重值列表
So our list of values is stored in v_1.
值列表存储在 v_1 中
Then using list comprehension,
然后根据列表推导式
I'm combining these weight values and our list of features into one data frame.
将这些权重值与特征列表变成一个 dataframe
So this will give me one row of weight values that correspond to specific feature names.
这个将提供对应于特定特征名称的一行权重值
So this gives me a data frame of components and then
这个将提供一个成分 dataframe
I actually want to sort this by weight value.
我希望按照权重值排序
I know I want to display the weights in order of importance.
我将按照重要性顺序显示权重
To find the most important weights,
为了查找最重要的权重
I'm going to look at the magnitude of each weight which is
我将查看每个权重的大小
the absolute value of the weight and then sort those values in order.
即权重的绝对值 然后对这些值排序
Here I'm going to be grabbing the top n weights.
在这里获取前 n 个权重
Finally, using the seaborne display library,
最后 使用 seaborn 显示库
I'm going to display a nice barplot that displays those weight values,
绘制一个条形图 其中显示了这些权重值
the names of the features,
特征名称
and has a title for the component number that I passed in.
并且包含所传入成分数量的标题
So let's actually see what this looks like for our first component.
看看最高成分的图形
Now, we know from before that this first component captures
我们知道最高成分可以解释
about 32 percent of the data variance in our training data.
训练数据中约 32% 的数据方差
We can see that it's extremely negatively weighted with respect
并且对于白人或在人口调查中确认为白人的人口来说
to white people or people who are counted and identified as white during the census.
权重为负并且为负的程度很高
It's positively weighted for people who identified as Hispanic or
对于西班牙裔或非裔人口来说权重为正
black and also positively weighted for levels of poverty and unemployment.
并且对于贫穷水平和就业水平来说也为正
We can go back to this function and pass in
我们可以回到该函数部分 传入更高的权重数量
more weights to display if we want a more granular look.
从而显示更精细的结果
We can see more detail about public and private work and labor type.
可以更详细地看到政府工作 私人工作和职业类型
One thing to note is that these individual features are not independent,
要注意的一点是 这些单个特征并非独立
and the discrete nature of these categories means that some data will always be left out.
这些类别的离散性表明有些数据始终被忽略
For example, racial dynamics and socioeconomic opportunities are often intertwined,
例如 种族和社会经济学机会经常交织在一起
making some of these features more correlated than others.
使某些特征的关系更紧密
These racial categories act as umbrella terms
这些种族类别充当涵盖性术语
that don't always capture the complexities of people's identities.
并不能始终发现人口的复杂性细节
As data scientists and machine learning developers,
作为数据科学家和机器学习开发人员
it's important to think about why this data is collected in
思考为何一开始要收集这样的数据
the first place and the limitations it has in describing a population.
以及它在描述人口方面有哪些限制很重要
Basically, I encourage you to look at any data source with a critical lens because
建议你用批判的眼光观察任何数据来源
that will give you a better idea of what insights you can eventually draw from this data.
这样可以更好地判断最终能从数据中发现什么样的规律
Let's check out another component.
我们再看一个成分
Now for our analysis,
在分析数据时
looking at the component breakdown,
查看成分细分信息
will be useful in generally describing how our training data is clustered later.
有助于了解稍后训练数据是如何聚类的
For example, when we create a reduced dimensionality data,
例如 在创建降维数据时
if we see that a certain US county has a high value for the component 2,
如果我们发现某个郡县的成分 2 值很高
we'll know that it has a mix of these positively and negatively weighted features.
我们就知道它是由这些正权重和负权重特征混合而成
So now you can use this function to look at the makeup of any component.
现在你可以使用该函数查看任何成分的组成了
Next, we'll actually deploy this PCA model,
接下来 我们将部署此 PCA 模型
grab our seven top components,
获取前七个成分
and create new dimensionality reduced training data.
并创建新的降维训练数据